Brandon Eugene Coplen

(571)-315-2285

brandon.coplen@gmail.com

github.com/brandoncoplen



COMPUTER SKILLS

- Programming Languages: Python, Java, PHP
- Web Development Languages: HTML, JavaScript, jQuery, CSS 3 and Bootstrap 5
- User interfaces include: Eclipse, Axure RP 9 and Microsoft Visual Studio 2019
- Proficient with Git, GitHub, pull requests and code reviews as well as working in an Agile Dev Environment.
- Experience in database MySQL
- Experience using Linux operating system to develop software and database management systems
- Experience programming a Cisco router as well as building a network on Google Cloud

EDUCATION

University of North Alabama, Florence, AL

Bachelor of Business Administration in Computer Information Systems

EXPERIENCE

Host, Logans Roadhouse, Florence, AL 2017-2018

- Greet Customers at door
- Seat Customers
- Bus Tables

Car Detailer, Self Employed, Florence, AL/Southport, NC 2016-present

- Offer a variety of services including wash, wax, scratch removal, etc.
- Manage Finances and product inventory
- Time management skills
- Valuable People skills

Student Organizations

Alpha Mu Lambda; Parliamentarian 2019-2021

Professional Summary

Proficient in skills such as groupwork, communication skills and maintaining a positive attitude. Has a wide area of computer and programming experience including an extensive knowledge in Microsoft Office.

- Leadership and engagement
- Versified programming language knowledge
- Experience using different development environments & IDEs
- Experience working with hardware
- Exceptional customer service skills